Afro-Palestinians are double oppressed. First as Palestinians, second because of our colors.
They call us kushi, niggers.
Well, I'm not surprised because discrimination and racism in the Israel society is an ideology.
As you know, in the Israel society, you have to be in groups.
The Oriental one is Faradim, the European one is Sheikh Nazim.
There are a lot of austerity in both groups.
But today, the most discriminated among those various groups are our people, the black Jews from Ethiopia.
Oh, that's right. They are the most discriminated.
Unbelievable, unbelievable. They wear the treatment.
And I know cases of those people, already 20 years in the country, still living in convoy, caravans.
But if you are an European Jew, blonde with blue eyes, maximum in one month you will be in a very bombarded apartment.
Wow!